<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.2</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 05:12:19 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Ep 77: Athlete Feature: Karthik Anand On His Marathon Journey From 5:20 Hours to Sub3</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;In this episode of Run with Fitpage, we had the opportunity to speak with renowned Indian runner Karthik Anand. Karthik is a runner for Team Pacemakers, based in Bangalore, and is an exceptional athlete and human being. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Karthik talks about his running journey, an inspiring one, from 5:20 to sub3-hours, while working full-time like most of us. He also told us about his nutrition and food choices, and how to sustain a sub3-hour time over a long period of time...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/1646863.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://chrt.fm/track/4E7BG4/www.buzzsprout.com/1646863/10954530-ep-77-athlete-feature-karthik-anand-on-his-marathon-journey-from-5-20-hours-to-sub3.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Cristy Lee Sets Her Sights and Talents on Much More Than What’s in Your Garage</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Known for her expertise fixing cars, trucks, and bikes, Cristy Lee, one of the most recognizable television personalities in the industry, sets her sights on breathing life into much more than what’s in your garage.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing renovation possibilities in the most unexpected, inexpensive properties,&amp;nbsp;Cristy will prove to clients that it’s worth the risk to buy low and spend high, while staying within budget in her new television series “Steal this House”...
Feed: https://feeds.podetize.com/rss/or8mheeESI</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://feeds.podetize.com/ep/XfnIWcN4E/media/xjvabj2eL.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>