<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod en</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 04:28:44 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Listen Now - REDACTED: Declassified Mysteries with Luke Lamana</title>
                <description>Behind the closed doors of government offices and military compounds, are hidden stories and buried secrets from the darkest corners of history. Each week, Luke Lamana, a Marine Corp Reconnaissance Veteran, pulls back the curtain on what once was classified information exposing the secrets and lies behind the world’s most powerful institutions. From the hitmakers at Wondery and Ballen Studios, we bring you REDACTED: Declassified Mysteries with Luke Lamana...
Feed: https://rss.art19.com/tides-of-history</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/pdst.fm/e/chrt.fm/track/9EE2G/rss.art19.com/episodes/87681c44-ab7f-4bbe-af4d-fc8187d8f091.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIhBmeXlkLXBvbGwtMQY6BkVU--0d7b418f62d9c36bf3b6fbcf0ff177ce88aec095"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Costco Kirkland Signature 2022 Napa Valley Red Blend Challenge (Napa vs. Bordeaux, Judgment of Paris)</title>
                <description>We generally have pretty good luck with Kirkland wines, and we put our good fortune to the test in this episode by tasting the 2022 Napa Valley Red Blend vs. two other Bordeaux-style blends. How did the Kirkland wine do?!? Well . . . we don’t want to give too many spoilers, but let&#39;s just say that we gave it a fair shot. We also dig into what exactly Bordeaux-style blends are because, let’s face it, when a wine says it is a “red blend” that could mean a whole bunch of things. So, we demystify...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/1880401.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1880401/episodes/16073666-costco-kirkland-signature-2022-napa-valley-red-blend-challenge-napa-vs-bordeaux-judgment-of-paris.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>