<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod zh</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2025 04:27:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Coldplay Kiss Cam Scandal: Kristin Cabot’s Ex-Husband Speaks Out</title>
                <description>Kristin Cabot’s estranged husband says they were already separated before her viral Coldplay kiss cam with Andy Byron. Charlie Sheen is teasing a Hollywood comeback, saying he has “something” new lined up after the success of his memoir and Netflix doc, while keeping details under wraps. Jacob Elordi and Olivia Jade sparked reconciliation rumors after showing up together at his Frankenstein premiere in Toronto, just a month after their split...
Feed: https://feeds.megaphone.fm/FOXM2059868704</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://pdst.fm/e/chrt.fm/track/25F5FC/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/traffic.megaphone.fm/FOXM6257661020.mp3?updated=1752001115"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Cybersecurity Situational Awareness Lessons from Mr. Robot</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;This episode of The Backup Wrap-up examines cybersecurity situational awareness through the lens of Mr. Robot&#39;s prison break episode. Curtis and Prasanna analyze the technical accuracy of USB stick attacks, Bluetooth car hacking, and social engineering tactics. The hosts discuss real-world defenses including USB port management, network segmentation, and employee training. They explore WPA2 encryption vulnerabilities and why upgrading to WPA3 matters for wireless security...
Feed: https://feeds.captivate.fm/backupwrapup/</description>
                
                
                <link>https://www.backupwrapup.com/cybersecurity-situational-awareness-mr-robot-ep6</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://episodes.captivate.fm/episode/1657d4bb-774a-4dc5-a9f7-759c35113111.mp3"/>
                <guid>https://www.backupwrapup.com/cybersecurity-situational-awareness-mr-robot-ep6</guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>