<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod zh</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2024 04:25:47 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>The Who What Wear Podcast: New York Fashion Week S/S 25 Report</title>
                <description>This fall’s New York Fashion Week just finished, so Editor in Chief Kat Collings and Editorial Director Lauren Eggertsen are here to break everything down. They’re covering their favorite shows, their new must-have pieces, and the trends they’re noticing, from flowy boho looks to sheer dressing and naked shoes. Plus, they talk about the week’s biggest shows, including a Ralph Lauren Polo Bar re-creation in the Hamptons and the first-ever fashion show at the Guggenheim museum.
Feed: https://rss.art19.com/second-life</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/rss.art19.com/episodes/ec5569c5-7840-4f1d-95e1-894d6468cc36.mp3?rss_browser=BAhJIhBmeXlkLXBvbGwtMQY6BkVU--0d7b418f62d9c36bf3b6fbcf0ff177ce88aec095"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Ep 357: OpenAI o1 released: 5 things to know about ChatGPT’s new model</title>
                <description>Send Everyday AI and Jordan a text messageOpenAI just shocked us all with the release of its o1 model, previously codenamed as Strawberry and Q* We break down what&#39;s new, 5 things you need to know and more! Newsletter: Sign up for our free daily newsletterMore on this Episode: Episode PageJoin the discussion: Ask Jordan and Hanan questions on AIUpcoming Episodes: Check out the upcoming Everyday AI Livestream lineupWebsite: YourEverydayAI.comEmail The Show: info@youreverydayai.comConnect ...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/2175779.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/2175779/15745490-ep-357-openai-o1-released-5-things-to-know-about-chatgpt-s-new-model.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>