<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod jp</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2023 04:25:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Welcome to E.125 How abandonment, torture and murder turned into empowerment and a movie.</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;How a man who experienced abandonment from his Father, leaving him at age 7, his mom being under investigation for torture against him, and his mom killing his step-dad, to a year in prison and now becoming an author, coach, and movie being filmed summer 2023. A story that will awaken you of how we cope with our fears in life, recover from PTSD, and trauma, and how we can become self-empowered to live our best lives regardless of our past!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; Tune in to receive the frequency...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/915826.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://chtbl.com/track/2CC95E/pdcn.co/e/www.buzzsprout.com/915826/12291305-welcome-to-e-125-how-abandonment-torture-and-murder-turned-into-empowerment-and-a-movie.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Building a Sustainable Platform and Pipeline for AAPI Leadership in Higher Education</title>
                <description>There is a glaring lack of Asian American and Pacific Islander (AAPI) representation in higher education leadership, although AAPIs may be well represented in the ranks of faculty and the student body. Participants will learn about the importance of creating a platform for collaboration and synergy among AAPI leaders who have reached the position of president/chancellor in higher education, and a sustainable pipeline to support ascending AAPI leaders.
Feed: https://www.aaari.info/mp3/</description>
                
                
                <link>http://www.aaari.info/mp3/./media/23-03-09Leadership.mp3</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="http://www.aaari.info/mp3/./media/23-03-09Leadership.mp3"/>
                <guid>http://www.aaari.info/mp3/./media/23-03-09Leadership.mp3</guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>