<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod en</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Jun 2025 04:32:45 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>When Love Turns Sour: How Celeb Divorces Affect Careers in the Entertainment Industry</title>
                <description>Celebrity relationships often live and die in the public eye, but what happens when love and business are deeply intertwined? On this episode of Indie Artist Music Hustle with Blonde Intelligence, we dive into the fascinating intersection of personal relationships and professional careers in the entertainment industry.  The spotlight falls on three high-profile Black celebrity couples experiencing public breakups: Cardi B and Offset, Remy Ma and Papoose, and Teyana Taylor and her husband. Eac...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/1172687.rss</description>
                
                
                <link>Http://www.Blonde-Intelligence.com</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1172687/episodes/17263223-when-love-turns-sour-how-celeb-divorces-affect-careers-in-the-entertainment-industry.mp3"/>
                <guid>Http://www.Blonde-Intelligence.com</guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>The Financial Crimes of Donald J. Trump October 23, 2020</title>
                <description>In this special episode of Mea Culpa Investigates we examine the full scope of corruption, financial crimes and sleazy conflicts of interest engendered by Donald Trump throughout his administration. Not only will you get a full preview of the legal reckoning that awaits him, but we take a deep dive into Trump&#39;s foreign entanglements to give you the full scope and magnitude of his blatant criminality...
Feed: https://audioboom.com/channels/5087881.rss</description>
                
                
                <link>https://audioboom.com/posts/8720987</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://pscrb.fm/rss/p/arttrk.com/p/ABMA5/dts.podtrac.com/redirect.mp3/audioboom.com/posts/8720987.mp3?modified=1747342869&amp;sid=5087881&amp;source=rss"/>
                <guid>https://audioboom.com/posts/8720987</guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>