<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod zh</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Thu, 24 Apr 2025 04:34:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Top Tips for Parenting, Health, Curiosity and Boundaries</title>
                <description>Join the conversation! Send Magic a text here! In this episode of &#39;A Magical Life,&#39; host Magic Barclay answers a listener&#39;s question on how to healthily raise children. The discussion covers crucial aspects such as nutrition, behavior, and learning. Magic emphasizes the importance of allowing kids to explore different foods, maintaining boundaries while understanding behavior, and making learning fun and interactive. She shares her experiences raising her own children, including two on the au...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/1156013.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1156013/episodes/16894948-top-tips-for-parenting-health-curiosity-and-boundaries.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Ep. 582 w/ Stacey Yudin CEO NEP Services</title>
                <description>&lt;p&gt;Our mission at NEP is to strengthen emergency responder departments and unions, nonprofit organizations, electrical unions, and teachers unions through the use of proprietary technology, time proven fundraising strategy, and brand building communications assistance that transcends traditional and social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEP is the leading fundraising, web, software, and media management company for Emergency Management, Non-Profit, Law Enforcement, Fire Associations, and Unions...
Feed: https://feeds.transistor.fm/building-the-future-show-radio-tv-podcast</description>
                
                
                <link>https://share.transistor.fm/s/b5bb65e5</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://op3.dev/e/media.transistor.fm/b5bb65e5/8edb40d1.mp3"/>
                <guid>https://share.transistor.fm/s/b5bb65e5</guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>