<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd">
        <channel>
            <title>Serendipod zh</title>
            <link>https://github.com/pschwede/serendipod</link>
            <atom:link href="https://raw.githubusercontent.com/pschwede/serendipod/main/feed.rss" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
            <description>Scraped from https://fyyd.de</description>
            
            <language>de-de</language>
            <copyright></copyright>
            <generator>serendipod 0.0.3</generator>
            <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Jun 2025 04:34:26 +0200</lastBuildDate>
            <item>
                <title>Unlocking The Secrets Of Full Body Orgasms – Milica Jelenic</title>
                <description>The Pleasure Zone with Milica Jelenic - Diamond Host Have you ever wondered what it would feel like to experience pleasure that moves through your entire body — not just a fleeting sensation, but a wave of energy that leaves you deeply connected, awakened, and alive? In this episode of The Pleasure Zone, we dive into the world of full body orgasms — what they are, how they differ from localized orgasms, and how you can begin to cultivate this powerful experience for yourself...
Feed: https://www.inspiredchoicesnetwork.com/xml-feed/?id=16939</description>
                
                
                <link>https://www.inspiredchoicesnetwork.com/media/unlocking-the-secrets-of-full-body-orgasms-milica-jelenic/</link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://icn-arc.s3.us-west-2.amazonaws.com/uploads/The_Pleasure_Zone_Jun_9_2025.mp3"/>
                <guid>https://www.inspiredchoicesnetwork.com/media/unlocking-the-secrets-of-full-body-orgasms-milica-jelenic/</guid>
                
            </item><item>
                <title>Sceptered Isle: The Story of the Fourteenth Century with Dr Helen Carr (ep 223)</title>
                <description>Fourteenth century England was a time of upheaval, extended war, political turmoil, and overall chaos. Dr Helen Carr joins us to talk about her new book that covers the life of the famous and lesser-known people of a time that changed power structures and the monarchy forever.  Show Notes:  Carol Ann Lloyd www.carolannlloyd.com @shakeuphistory patreon.com/carolannlloyd The Tudors by Numbers Courting the Virgin Queen   Dr Helen Carr helencarr.com @helenhcarr History Hit, Intelligence Squa...
Feed: https://feeds.buzzsprout.com/1129166.rss</description>
                
                
                <link></link>
                <enclosure type="audio/mpeg" length="1" url="https://www.buzzsprout.com/1129166/episodes/17266761-sceptered-isle-the-story-of-the-fourteenth-century-with-dr-helen-carr-ep-223.mp3"/>
                <guid></guid>
                
            </item>
        </channel>
</rss>